{
    "subject": "resource/Randy_Quaid",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Houston",
    "human_readable": "Randy Quaid was born in Houston.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9221750497817993,
            "question": "Where was Randy Quaid born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8143222332000732,
            "question": "When was Randy Quaid born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7198793292045593,
            "question": "Where did Randy Quaid grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3898729681968689,
            "question": "Is Randy Quaid known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3502282202243805,
            "question": "What are some notable roles played by Randy Quaid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33102935552597046,
            "question": "What is Randy Quaid's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3123076558113098,
            "question": "Is Randy Quaid related to any other actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2883550226688385,
            "question": "What is Randy Quaid known for besides acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20425984263420105,
            "question": "Has Randy Quaid won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19515778124332428,
            "question": "In what films has Randy Quaid starred?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Randy Quaid was born in Houston.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7377_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Randy Quaid won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7377_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Randy Quaid known for besides acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7377_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Randy Quaid related to any other actors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7377_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7377_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents provided contain multiple instances of information about Randy Quaid's birthplace, which all confirm that he was born in Houston, Texas. For example, from file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7377/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt: \"Randy Quaid (born Randall Rudy Quaid on October 1, 1950 in Houston, Texas)...\" and from file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7377/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt: \"Born Oct 1, 1950 in Houston, Texas, USA\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references confirming that Randy Quaid was indeed born in Houston, Texas."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}